Chandler, Alfred D., 1918-2007. Papers, 1941-2004: A Finding Aid
Alfred D. Chandler papers, 1940-2007
- Series II. Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Johns Hopkins University, 1949-1978
  - Subseries B. MIT Research and Writing, 1949-1967
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Bibliography, Railroads, Miscellaneous (Box 24, f. 3)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Old Charts, Chicago and Rock Island (Box 24, f. 4)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Chicago and Northwestern, Atchinson, Topeka and Santa Fe (Box 24, f. 5)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: B&O, Organizational Structure, 1826-1860 (Box 24, f. 6)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Final Charts, 1865-1900; Notes, 1865-1889 (Box 24, f. 7)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Charts, Baltimore and Ohio RR Company Rule (Box 24, f. 8)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Charts, Organizational Structure, 1910-1955 (Box 24, f. 9)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: Various (Box 24, f. 10)
    - Early Visible Hand Research: The McLane Report by Alfred D. Chandler III (Box 24, f. 11)
    - Cole Volume: Outline of Work and Bibliographical Data (Box 24, f. 12)
    - Cole Volume: Outline of Lecture Delivered by A. H. Cole at Oxford, 1953 (Box 24, f. 13)
    - Cole Volume: General Data (Box 24, f. 14)
    - Cole Volume: General Data for Part II—Early, Essay for Rostow (Box 24, f. 15-16)
    - Cole Volume: Tables on Railroad Mileage (Box 24, f. 17)
    - Cole Volume: DuPont Miscellaneous (Box 24, f. 18-19)
    - Cole Volume: Charts (Box 24, f. 20)
    - Cole Volume: Walter Carpenter Material (Box 25, f. 1)
    - Cole Volume: Chapter 7, Miscellaneous (Box 25, f. 2)
    - Cole Volume: Chapter 4 (Box 25, f. 3)
    - Cole Volume: Chapter 5 (Box 25, f. 4)
    - Cole Volume: Chapter 6 (Box 25, f. 5-6)
    - Cole Volume: Manufacturing Firms (Box 25, f. 7-8)
    - Cole Volume: Information for 20c. Volumes (Box 25, f. 9-10)
    - Cole Volume: Executive Committee, etc. (Box 25, f. 11)
    - Cole Volume: Colonial Data (Box 25, f. 12)
    - Cole Volume: Finance and Insurance (Box 25, f. 13)
    - Cole Volume: Railroad Strategy abt., 1873 (Box 25, f. 14)
    - Cole Volume: Pennsylvania NY Central Summaries (Box 25, f. 15-16)
    - Cole Volume: Cole’s Manuscript, Chapter 11, 1964 (Box 26, f. 1)
    - Cole Volume: Cole’s Manuscript, Chapter 12, 1964 (Box 26, f. 2)
    - Cole Volume: Cole’s Manuscript, Chapter 13, 1964 (Box 26, f. 3)
    - Cole Volume: Cole’s Manuscript, Chapter 14, 1964 (Box 26, f. 4)
    - Cole Volume: Cole’s "The Business System and Economic Advance" (Box 26, f. 5)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section I: The Colonial Years: Chapter 1 (Box 26, f. 6)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section I: Chapter 2 (Box 26, f. 7)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section II: 1775-1850: Chapter 3 (Box 26, f. 8)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section II: Chapter 4 (Box 26, f. 9)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section II: Chapter 5 (Box 26, f. 10)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section II: Chapter 6 (Box 26, f. 11)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section III: 1850-1914: Chapter 7 (Box 26, f. 12)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure" Section III: Chapter 8 (Box 26, f. 13)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section III: Chapter 9 (Box 26, f. 14)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section III: Chapter 10 (Box 26, f. 15)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section III: Chapter 11 (Box 26, f. 16)
    - Cole – "The Evolution of the Business Structure": Section III: Chapter 12 (Box 26, f. 17)
    - General Motors Story [published as My Years with General Motors by Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. (1964)]: Correspondence, Notes, Drafts, etc. (Box 27, f. 1-5)
    - General Motors Story [published as My Years with General Motors by Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. (1964)]: GM Facts and Figures, 1920-1954 (Box 238, f. 8)
    - General Motors Story: 1st Draft: Contents, Outline, Introduction, 1956-1957 (Box 27, f. 6)
    - General Motors Story: 1st Draft: Chapter 1, 1956 (Box 27, f. 7)
    - General Motors Story: 1st Draft: Chapter 2, 1956 (Box 27, f. 8)
    - General Motors Story: 1st Draft: Chapter 3, 1956 (Box 27, f. 9)
    - General Motors Story: Summary, Introduction, 1958 (Box 27, f. 10)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 1, 1958 (Box 27, f. 11)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 2, 1958 (Box 27, f. 12)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 3, 1958 (Box 27, f. 13)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 4, 1958 (Box 27, f. 14)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 5, 1958 (Box 27, f. 15)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 6, 1958 (Box 27, f. 16)
    - General Motors Story: Chapter 7 and Comments, 1958 (Box 27, f. 17)
  - Subseries C. MIT Research and Writing: Alfred P. Sloan Autobiography - General Motors, 1954-1960
    This subseries consists of Alfred Chandler’s correspondence and research materials relating to the writing of Alfred P. Sloan’s My Years with General Motors (1964). Chandler was consulting historian and research associate to Sloan from 1956 to 1960. He regularly corresponded with Sloan and his editors, John McDonald and Catharine Stevens. The research materials include Chandler’s notes, copies of General Motors' correspondence, reports, legal papers, published documents, and transcriptions of interviews. It also includes rough drafts of several chapters from the book.
    The material in this subseries is in the original order.
    This subseries was donated by Alfred Chandler in 1971 and was previously cataloged with the Baker Library Historical Collections Manuscripts Collection (Manuscript call number MSS: 534 1908-1960).
    - Drafts: Chandler General Motors - Contents of Files (Box 27, f. 18)
    - Notes: General Motors General Notes: Alfred D. Chandler (Box 27, f. 19)
    - Notes: General Motors Story Research (Box 27, f. 20)
    - Notes: DuPont: Notes, I (Mel Longwood Data) (Box 27, f. 21)
    - Notes: Notes, Pt II: Diversification (Box 27, f. 22)
    - Notes: General Motors: Revised, Pt. III (Box 27, f. 23-24)
    - Notes: Part I - Durant and Storrow Period, 1908-1915; Notes on Early Organization (Box 28, f. 1-7)
    - Notes: Part I: Executive and Financial Committees (and Reports) (Box 28, f. 8)
    - Notes: The Reports - Alaska Rejects (Retitled from "1912, Apr-June") (Box 28, f. 9)
    - Notes: Part I - General Motors Revised (Box 28, f. 10-12)
    - Notes: Chapter IV: GM Industry (Box 28, f. 13)
    - Notes: General Motors Organization, 1924 (with files removed for check in Wilmington) (Box 28, f. 14)
    - Notes: General Motors Revisions - General (Box 28, f. 15)
    - Notes: Part 4 and 5, 1925-1937 - General Letters (Box 28, f. 16)
    - Comments: On Book (Box 28, f. 17-18)
    - Comments: GMC Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 28, f. 19-24)
    - Correspondence - re Book: Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: McDonald Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 28, f. 25-29)
    - Correspondence - re Book: Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Donaldson Brown to Alfred Sloan, Hist. of GM Management, 1/14/55 (Box 28, f. 30)
    - Correspondence - re Book: Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Sloan’s Recent Corres. on GMC Organ., 1954-1957 (Box 28, f. 31-32)
    - Correspondence - re Book: Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Sloan’s Recent Corres. on GMC Organ., 1954-1957 (Box 29, f. 1-5)
    - Documents: Including Sloan Reports: Index Letters, 1926-1940 (Box 29, f. 6-8)
    - Documents: Including Sloan Reports: Annual Reports, Prices; Organization, 1911 (Box 29, f. 9-10)
    - Separate Reports - Institutional Advertising, Inventories – Pratt, etc.,1920-25 (Box 29, f. 11)
    - Organization Report - Sloan (Box 29, f. 12)
    - War Adm. and War Emergency,1940-1946 (Box 29, f. 13)
    - Raskob Documents, 1905 (Box 29, f. 14)
    - Documents, 1908-1956 (Box 29, f. 15-16)
    - Orgn. Procedure, 1929 (Box 29, f. 17-18)
    - 10 Point Program, 1932 (Box 29, f. 19-20)
    - GM General Letters, 1937-1948 (Box 29, f. 21)
    - Thermofax of Documents-Copy 2 (Box 29, f. 22-26)
    - Manuscripts Chapter - Direction, GM; Contribution to GM; Corporate Citizenship (Box 30, f. 1-4)
    - Papers by Alfred D. Chandler (Box 30, f. 5)
    - Ch. 5 and 6 Notes (Box 30, f. 6-8)
    - Ch. 6 GM Policy and Administration (Box 30, f. 9-10)
    - Data and Manuscripts on Early Shift Reorganization (Box 30, f. 11)
    - Finance (Box 30, f. 12-14)
    - Correspondence-re: Book: Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Manuscript p. 51 (Box 30, f. 15-17)
    - Ch. 4 The Market; Text, Outlines and Summary Notes (Box 30, f. 18-22)
    - Written Summaries with Footnotes, 1921-25 (Box 31, f. 1-3)
    - Ch. 3 Notes, Summary and Research: Reports (Box 31, f. 4-7)
    - Report on Durant - Expansion (Box 31, f. 8)
    - Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Ch. 3, 4 and General Data (Box 31, f. 9-10)
    - Drafts-Ch. 4 and 5 (Box 31, f. 11)
    - Drafts Ch. 2 (Box 31, f. 12)
    - Correspondence - re Book: Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Drafts - Notes from McDonald’s Draft (Box 31, f. 1-14)
    - Incl. Ltrs to Sloan: Drafts Evolution of the Policy Groups (Box 31, f. 15)
    - Drafts-Ch. 5 (Box 31, f. 16-20)
    - Drafts-Ch. 6; Notes from DuPont Anti-trust Suit (Box 31, f. 21-23)
    - Articles and Reports-A.P. Sloan, Jr., 1926-1940 (Box 31, f. 24-27)
    - Documents-Incl. Sloan Reports: Alfred D. Chandler Jr. Interviews with Sloan (Box 31, f. 28-31)
    - Documents 1919-1921; DuPont-1918, 1919-Changes (Box 32, f. 1-3)
    - Documents 1919-1921; DuPont-1920-1921-Notes Ch. 4, Pt. 1 (Box 32, f. 4-7)
    - Documents-Suit; Defendant; Government: Trial Documents-Defendant (Box 32, f. 8-12)
    - Documents-Suit; Defendant; Government: DuPont Testimonies (Box 32, f. 13)
    - Documents-Suit; Defendant; Government: Trial Documents-Government; Top Committee-Pair 6 (Box 32, f. 14-17)
    - Documents-Suit; Defendant; Government: Trial-DuPont Final photos on paint on anti-trust (Box 32, f. 18)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Reports and Memos, 1922 (Box 32, f. 19)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Administration Committee, 1937-1940; Administration, etc., 1941-War (Box 32, f. 20-22)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Distribution Policy Group, 1937 (Box 32, f. 23-25)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Engineering Policy Group, 1937 (Box 32, f. 26-27)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Executive Committee Minutes, 1919-1920 (Box 32, f. 28)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: GMC The Executive Comm.-Ch. 4, 1919-1937 (Box 33, f. 1-6)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Executive Committee Organization, 1926-1936 (Box 33, f. 7-8)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Executive Committee, 1921-25, GMC (Box 33, f. 9-11)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Executive Committee, 1925-1937 (Box 33, f. 12-14)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Finance Committee, 1920 (Box 33, f. 15-16)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Executive Committee, 1921-1925 (Box 33, f. 17-19)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Policy Committee, 1937-1940; 1942-1946 (Box 33, f. 20)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Operating Committee, 1921-1931 (Box 33, f. 21)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Product Group, 1937-1944 (Box 33, f. 22)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Purchasing Committee, 1922-1929 (Box 33, f. 23)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: General Sales Committee, 1925-1932 (Box 33, f. 24-25)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Works Manager, Power and Maintenance Committees, 1925-1928 (Box 33, f. 26)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: General Technical Committee, 1923-1932, GMC (Box 33, f. 27)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Top Committees, 1942-1946 (Box 33, f. 28)
    - Documents, Committee Reports: Donaldson Brown Interview (Box 33, f. 29-31)
    - Copy: "The development of a Basic Purchasing Power Index by Counties": Sales Section, General Motors, circa 1928 (Box 34, f. 1)
    - Original: "The development of a Basic Purchasing Power Index by Counties": Sales Section, General Motors, circa 1928 (Box 34, f. 2)
    - Interviews: DuPont Interviews - Including Brown’s Book (Box 34, f. 3)
    - Interviews: Interview - R.H. Grant (Box 34, f. 4)
    - Interviews: Interviews Ch. 4 (Box 34, f. 5)
    - Interviews: Sloan - Interview and Speeches (Box 34, f. 6)
    - Research by Others: Adam Stricker: 1950 (Box 34, f. 7)
    - Research by Others: General Motors Story Reels (Box 34, f. 8-9)
    - Research by Others: Advisory Staff Operations, 1920-1929 (Box 34, f. 10)
    - Research by Others: Products Groups, 1955; also Product Study Groups, Product Program (Box 34, f. 11-12)
    - Charts, Tables: Organization Charts (Box 34, f. 13-16)
    - Charts, Tables: Charts and Tables (Box 34, f. 17)
    - Charts, Tables: Policy Group Charts (Box 34, f. 18)
    - Printed Material: Printed Items (Box 35, f. 1-5)
    - Printed Material: Data GM/Ford - Useful for P.S. du Pont biography (Box 35, f. 6)
  - Subseries D. MIT Administration and Program, 1953-1963
    This subseries consists of administrative records kept by Alfred Chandler while teaching at MIT and includes correspondence, memos, minutes, reports, and printed material documenting committees and programs.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Agenda, Committee on, 1959-1960 (Box 35, f. 7)
    - Ad Hoc History Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 35, f. 8)
    - Course 21, 1959 (Box 35, f. 9)
    - Empires: Proposals for Enlarged Role for History at MIT (Box 35, f. 10)
    - Finding Committee, 1962 (Box 35, f. 11)
    - Graduation Exercises, 1963 (Box 35, f. 12)
    - History Sequences (Box 35, f. 13)
    - Humanities, Department of, 1961-1962 (Box 35, f. 14-15)
    - Humanities, Department of: Information, 1960 (Box 35, f. 16)
    - Humanities, Department of: Reprint Series, 1962 (Box 35, f. 17)
    - Humanities, Department of: School Council Meetings, 1961-1962 (Box 35, f. 18)
    - Industrial Studies Project, 1960 (Box 35, f. 19)
    - MIT Data, 1953-1957 (Box 35, f. 20)
    - President’s Office, 1953-1962 (Box 35, f. 21)
    - Social Sciences, Committee on the (Box 36, f. 1-6)
  - Subseries E. MIT Teaching, 1951-1962
    This subseries consists of lecture notes, syllabi, reading lists, exam questions, readings, and memoranda and other material from courses taught by Alfred Chandler while teaching at MIT.
    Arranged chronologically by course and chronologically within each course.
    - E11: Course Description, 1951 (Box 36, f. 7)
    - E11: Class Notes, 1951-1952 (Box 36, f. 8-9)
    - E12 (H12): Syllabus, Course Description, Readings, 1951-1953 (Box 36, f. 10)
    - H12: Lecture Notes, 1953 (Box 36, f. 11-18)
    - H12: Course Description, Lecture Notes, Readings, 1953 (Box 37, f. 1)
    - Hist. of Managing in the U.S.: Course Outline, 1960 (Box 37, f. 2)
    - H51-52: Exams, Paper Topics, Tables, 1955-1958 (Box 37, f. 3)
    - H51: Reading and Lecture Notes, etc., 1954 (Box 37, f. 4)
    - H52: Notes, etc., 1955 (Box 37, f. 5-7)
    - H51-52: Syllabi, Exams, 1956-1957 (Box 37, f. 8)
    - H52: Lecture Notes, 1957-1958 (Box 37, f. 9-10)
    - H52: Assorted Materials (also 21.44), 1957-1960 (Box 37, f. 11-13)
    - H51: Data for, 1957-1958 (Box 37, f. 14)
    - 21.43: Lectures, etc., 1956-1960 (Box 38, f. 1-2)
    - 21.44: Lectures, 1959 (Box 38, f. 3)
    - 21.43: Lecture Notes, 1960 (Box 38, f. 4-5)
    - 21.43: Essential Data, etc., 1960-1962 (Box 38, f. 5)
    - 21.43: Notes, 1962 (Box 38, f. 7)
    - 21.44: Notes, etc., 1960 (Box 38, f. 8)
    - 21.44: Class Notes (1961), etc., 1958-1961 (Box 38, f. 9-11)
    - 21.41: Lectures (1961), etc., 1955-1961 (Box 38, f. 12-14)
    - H21: Lecture Notes, undated (Box 39, f. 1)
    - H21: Readings, The United States: Men and Issues, undated (2 copies) (Box 252, f. 1-2)
    - H21: Readings, The United States: Men and Issues, 1956 (2 copies) (Box 252, f. 3-4)
    - H21: Lecture Notes, etc., 1953-1954 (Box 39, f. 2-3)
    - H22: Notes, etc., 1954 (Box 39, f. 4-5)
    - H21: Lecture Notes, 1955-1957 (Box 39, f. 6-8)
    - H22: Materials, 1955-1956 (Box 39, f. 9-10)
    - H21-22: Materials, 1956 (Box 39, f. 11)
    - Glass negatives, ca. 1956 (Box 254, f. 6)
      These negatives are restricted until reformatted. See Archivist for more information
    - H21-22: Planning: Both Versions, etc., 1955-1958 (Box 40, f. 1)
    - H21-22: Planning etc., 1955-1957 (Box 40, f. 2-3)
    - H22: Part I: (1956) Notes and Earlier, 1955-1956 (Box 40, f. 4-7)
    - H22: (1956) Notes from Earlier, 1954-1956 (Box 40, f. 8-10)
    - H22: Readings, The United States: Men and Issues, 1957 (Box 253, f. 1)
    - H21: Notes and Essential Mimeograph Data, 1957 (Box 40, f. 11-12)
    - 21.03-21.04: (H21-22): Teaching Memos, etc., 1955-1960 (Box 40, f. 13)
    - 21.03-21.04: New Core Course, Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 40, f. 14)
    - 21.03-21.04: Modern World, 1960-1961 (Box 41, f. 1-3)
    - 21.03: Readings, The United States: Men and Issues, 1958 (Box 252, f. 5)
    - 21.04: Readings, The United States: Men and Issues, 1957 (Box 252, f. 6)
    - 15.201: U.S. Political Economy, Fall 1959 (Box 41, f. 4-6)
  - Subseries F. MIT External Activities: Teaching, 1954-1963
    This subseries consists of lecture notes, photocopied material, and correspondence from courses taught by Alfred Chandler at various institutions while teaching at MIT. This subseries includes materials from classes taught at the Naval War College on basic national strategy, Northwestern University on transportation history, General Electric and IBM.
    - Naval War College, 1954 (Box 41, f. 7)
    - Northwestern Course, 1957 (Box 41, f. 8-9)
    - General Electric Advanced Management Course, May 26, 1960 (Box 41, f. 10)
    - IBM Executive Development School, June 1962 and Feb. 1963 (Box 41, f. 11-12)
  - Subseries G. MIT External Activities: Conferences, 1956-1963
    This subseries consists of material from conferences attended by Alfred Chandler while teaching at MIT and includes papers by others, outlines of Chandler's comments, correspondence, and printed materials.
    Arranged chronologically by date of event.
    - ASEE, June 1956 (Box 41, f. 13)
    - AHA, Dec. 30, 1956 (Box 41, f. 14)
    - DuPont Symposium, June 17-27, 1957 (Box 42, f. 1-2)
    - American Historical Association (AHA), Dec. 28, 1958 (Box 42, f. 3)
    - ASEE, Pittsburgh, June 17, 1959 (Box 42, f. 4)
    - Lecture: The History of Managing in the U.S., May 26, 1960 (Box 42, f. 5)
    - Economic History Association (EHA), Sept. 9, 1960 (Box 42, f. 6)
    - Talk: "Westward Through the Islands", Feb. 23, 1961 (Box 42, f. 7)
    - Conference on the Role of Social Sciences, April 26, 1961 (Box 42, f. 8)
    - Northwestern University: Conference on Business History, Feb. 16, 1963 (Box 42, f. 9)
    - Mississippi Valley Historical Association, May 3-4, 1963 (Box 42, f. 10)
  - Subseries H. MIT External Activities: Memberships, 1957-1963
    This subseries consists of material from of Alfred D. Chandler's association with various boards, committees, societies, associations, and businesses while teaching at MIT. This subseries includes correspondence, minutes and reports, printed material, clippings, applications, and evaluations.
    Arranged chronologically.
    - Association for Higher Education: Conference of Higher Education (July 1961), 1961-1962 (Box 42, f. 11-13)
    - Association for Higher Education: Correspondence (etc.), 1962 (Box 42, f. 14)
    - Association for Higher Education: Correspondence (etc.), 1962-1963 (Box 42, f. 15)
    - Association for Higher Education: Executive Committee Meeting, Oct. 1962 (Box 43, f. 1)
    - Association for Higher Education: Executive Committee Meetings, March 1963 (Box 43, f. 2)
    - Association for Higher Education: Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 43, f. 3)
    - Beveridge Committee: Form, Stationery, undated (Box 43, f. 4)
    - Beveridge Committee Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 43, f. 5)
    - Beveridge Committee Evaluations, 1957 (Box 43, f. 6)
    - Beveridge Committee Evaluations, 1958-1959 (Box 43, f. 7)
    - Business History Foundation, 1959-1963 (Box 43, f. 8-10)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1957-1961 (Box 43, f. 11)
    - Park School: Correspondence and Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 43, f. 12)
    - Park School: New Building, 1962 (Box 43, f. 13)
    - Park School: Printed Material, 1957-1963 (Box 43, f. 14)
    - Schenkman Publishing Company: Correspondence, etc., 1961-1963 (Box 43, f. 15)
    - Schenkman Publishing Company: Report, 1962 (Box 43, f. 16)
    - Schenkman Publishing Company: Report, 1962-1963 (Box 43, f. 17)
  - Subseries I. Johns Hopkins University Correspondence and Subject Files, 1963-1978
    This subseries consists of correspondence to and from Alfred Chandler while teaching at Johns Hopkins University where he taught from 1963-1970. Correspondents include Chandler's students, colleagues, fellow scholars, family, and friends. Topics addressed include Chandler's own writing and research as well as that of others, conferences, publications, and job openings. The material in the series includes letters, printed material, and photocopies.
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - A: Adams-Aydelotte, 1964-1971 (Box 44, f. 2)
    - Ambrose, Stephen and A.D.C.: Press Briefing Tape [Reel to reel tape] (Box 44, f. 3)
    - Ambrose, Stephen, 1965-1969 (Box 44, f. 4)
    - Andreano, Ralph L., 1964-1969 (Box 44, f. 5)
    - B: Baltimore-Bobbs Merrill Company, Inc., 1964-1971 (Box 44, f. 6)
    - B: Bockman-Burden, 1964-1971 (Box 44, f. 7)
    - Barker, J.M., 1967-1971 (Box 44, f. 8)
    - Baughman, James P., 1967-1971 (Box 44, f. 9)
    - Benton, George S. (Dean), 1970-1971 (Box 44, f. 10)
    - Black and Decker History Project, 1969-1970 (Box 44, f. 11)
    - Blum, John M., 1965-1969 (Box 44, f. 12)
    - Boston Management Consulting Group, 1966 (Box 44, f. 13)
    - Bruchey, Stuart, 1965-1971 (Box 44, f. 14)
    - C: Cameron-Columbia University, 1964-1971 (Box 44, f. 15)
    - C: Congress of the U.S.-Cushing, 1966-1970 (Box 44, f. 16)
    - Cambridge Economic History (Peter Mathias), 1969-1971 (Box 44, f. 17)
    - Cameron, Rondo, 1969-1971 (Box 44, f. 18)
    - Canada Council, 1969-1970 (Box 44, f. 19)
    - Carnegie, Andrew (Dictionary of American Biography ), 1970 (Box 44, f. 20)
    - Challener, Richard, 1970 (Box 44, f. 21)
    - Chandler, Mrs. Alfred D., Sr., 1966 (Box 44, f. 22)
    - Chavenon, Pierre, 1969-1971 (Box 44, f. 23)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 44, f. 24)
    - Cochran, Thomas, 1968-1971 (Box 44, f. 25)
    - Cole, Arthur (Meso-Economics), undated (Box 44, f. 26)
    - Cole, Arthur H., 1963 (Box 45, f. 1)
    - Cole, Arthur H., 1964 (Box 45, f. 2)
    - Cole, Arthur H., 1965-1966 (Box 45, f. 3)
    - Cole, Arthur H., 1967-1970 (Box 45, f. 4)
    - Crooks, James B., 1966-1968 (Box 45, f. 5)
    - Crowl, Philip, 1966-1968 (Box 45, f. 6)
    - D: Davis-Dupree,1964-1971 (Box 45, f. 7)
    - Dale, Ernest,1964-1969 (Box 45, f. 8)
    - Dictionary of American Biography, 1966-1968 (Box 45, f. 9)
    - Douglas, Richard, 1964-1967 (Box 45, f. 10)
    - E: Ebner-Ewald, 1964-1970 (Box 45, f. 11)
    - Eichner, Alfred, 1968-1971 (Box 45, f. 12)
    - Eleutherian Mills, 1964-1969 (Box 45, f. 13)
    - F: Faissler-Freedom Foundation, 1960-1971 (Box 45, f. 14)
    - Ford Foundation, 1969 (Box 45, f. 15)
    - G: Galgano-Glazier, 1964-1971 (Box 45, f. 16)
    - G: Golden Spike Centennial-Guillebean, 1964-1971 (Box 45, f. 17)
    - Galambos, Louis, 1967-1968 (Box 45, f. 18)
    - Green, E.R.R., 1964-1968 (Box 45, f. 19)
    - Greene, Jack P., 1971 (Box 45, f. 20)
    - Guana Island Club (personal), 1957-1972 (Box 246, f. 16)
    - Guttman, Herbert, 1964-1968 (Box 45, f. 21)
    - H: Hall-Hessen, 1964-1971 (Box 45, f. 22)
    - H: Hickerson-Holland, 1966-1970 (Box 45, f. 23)
    - H: Holmes-Hyman, 1965-1971 (Box 45, f. 24)
    - Halleck, Henry (General), undated (Box 46, f. 1)
    - Harcourt Brace and World, 1963-1975 (Box 46, f. 2)
    - Harcourt Brace and World, 1962-1978 (Box 46, f. 3)